But, do you know the connection between
Tyler's I Ain't Got Time
>> I ain't got time.
>> and Deee-Lite's 1990 classic Groove Is
in the Heart?
>> Groove is in the heart.
>> I don't.
>> Not a song you would think has any
connection, but if you listen to the
intro of Groove Is in the Heart, you'll
hear this.
>> [music]
>> We're going to dance and have some fun.
>> So, you recognize that?
>> Yeah.
>> He heard this song on the radio and must
have heard that little part. He went
down the rabbit hole of like, what is
that sample? Turns out it is from The
Art of Belly Dancing. It's a like
instructional belly dancing vinyl record
from 1969.
>> [music]
>> This would be something that Tyler
would love.
>> And so, let's hear now what he does with
it, which is totally transforms it.
The bass is just
knocked so hard.
But, even the percussion stuff is so
cool, like him just kind of
>> This is definitely [music] like a
Timbaland record.
>> Oh, that's a good That's actually
>> you know who he offered this beat to
first before he rapped on it?
>> Was it Oh, Kanye, like Pablo.
>> so this song started, I think, in a
session for Life of Pablo.
>> Yes.
>> Kanye rejects it. Then he tries to give
it to Nicki Minaj.
>> He sounded so hurt.